[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The horns of which giraffes are very often bald on top?", "correct_answer": "Males", "incorrect_answers": ["Babies", "Females", "Very old giraffes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that the only weapon Chewie uses in Star Wars is his bowcaster?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which continent is the island of Madagascar part of?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Asia", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many types of skin are there depending on skins reaction to UV-radiation?", "correct_answer": "6 types", "incorrect_answers": ["4 types", "3 types", "5 types"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the word labeorphilist?", "correct_answer": "A collector of beer bottles", "incorrect_answers": ["A lover of experimental science", "A flower that eats insects", "An animal that is attracted to sweet smells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What airport is the largest hub of United Airlines?", "correct_answer": "OHare in Chicago", "incorrect_answers": ["Metropolitan in Detroit", "Dallas Fort Worth", "La Guardia in New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She was Johnny Carsons first guest on The Tonight Show with Johnny Carson.", "correct_answer": "Joan Crawford", "incorrect_answers": ["Bette Midler", "Joan Rivers", "Judy Garland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the correct plural form of Attorney General?", "correct_answer": "Attorneys General", "incorrect_answers": ["Attorney Generals", "Attorneyes Generales", "Attorneys Generals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What brand is the little red two-door car, that Eve uses to travel to northern California in the film Eve of Destruction.", "correct_answer": "Ford Mustang", "incorrect_answers": ["Chevy Nova", "Dodge Charger", "Chevy Camaro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Keep off the grass in diner-speak means this.", "correct_answer": "Hold the lettuce", "incorrect_answers": ["Tomato only", "Like the sign says...", "No parsley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, what would the per capita income (in USD, Atlas method) of the villagers be?", "correct_answer": "$7000", "incorrect_answers": ["$12500", "$45000", "$26000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did the CERN laboratory in Geneva, Switzerland, produce for the first time in 1996?", "correct_answer": "Antimatter", "incorrect_answers": ["An atom without electrons", "A black hole", "An atom without protons"]}]